When they gave out eyes like diamonds
That would shame the stars that shine
My darling, my darling
You were the first in line
When they gave out lips like honey
That hold a new thrill every time
My darling, my darling
You were the first in line
There may be others that know you longer
Who pledge their hearts to you
But there's no other could love you stronger
Any stronger than I do
Don't refuse me, say you'll choose me
I'm yours, oh please be mine
My darling, say I'm your darling
The first and the last in line
There may be others that know you longer
Who pledge their hearts to you
But there's no other could love you stronger
Any stronger than I do
Don't refuse me, say you'll choose me
I'm yours, oh please be mine
My darling, say I'm your darling
The first and the last in line