You came smiling softly, shining moonbeam
Easy as a dreamer into my world
And before I realized the danger
I found myself staring into your eyes
Somewhere in their colors I saw promises
Of things I'd never seen before
It's all over
I've got to have you
Holding on to talk and saying nothing
Knowin' in a moment I could lose you
Then without a warning I remembered
That you trembled at the touch of my hand
Knowin' when you came to me that no one else
Would ever feel the same
In my arms
It's all over
I've got to have you
Waking in the morning with the tenderness
Of holding you asleep in my arms
Dreaming while your hair was blowing
Softer than a whisper on my cheek
I don't know the feeling
So I don't know if it's love
But it's enough, It's enough
It's all over
I've got to have you
And I can't help it