She stands by the lights at the front of the audience.
Smile on her face, just taking in their every glance
She loves the way they love her
And she smiles
She loves every sweet talking lie
Then a smooth talking baby-faced man
from the management
Trips on the wire as he's paying her a compliment.
She loves the way he loves her
And she smiles
She loves every sweet talking lie
Crying, dying, sighing while she's shining in the microphone
Kings and Queens of future time when she and me are all alone
She loves the way I love her
And she smiles
She loves every sweet talking lie
Running my hands through her hair
And knowing she'll always be there
She loves the way they love her
She loves the way
She smiles