When you're thirsty and no one will fill your cup for you
And your well-dressed friends don't want you on their street
When you're so far down, the gutter looks like up to you
I will still be kneeling at your feet
When you can't remember where you left your laughter
And you forget the definition of your name
When your yesterday sets fire to your ever after
I'll reach down and pull you from the flames
When all the crippled children you give strength to
Lay their crutches down and walk away
And you realize that all their mothers hate you
I'll be there to hear the things you say
When at last your bitter problems all ignore you
And you've come out clean, everything is done
And you realize I've been through it all before you
Come down and walk beside me in the sun